A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1909-1974; 200; 28 Cubic Feet; 69 __Boxes __28 cubic feet
  - United States - Medical Sciences, 1913-1965; 200.A; 51 __Boxes __20 cubic feet
    - University of Buffalo - Clark, William T. - Visit, Public Health, 1936 (Box 111, Folder 1363)
    - University of Colorado - Darley, Ward - Visit, Public Health, 1946-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1364)
    - University of Colorado - Darley, Ward - Visit, Public Health - Report, 1947 (Box 111, Folder 1365)
    - University of Denver - Speech Defects - Study, 1942-1947 (Box 111, Folder 1366)
    - University of Georgia - Psychiatry, 1936-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1367)
    - University of Georgia - Psychiatry, 1936-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1368)
    - University of Illinois - Legal Medicine, 1946-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1369)
    - University of Illinois - Legal Medicine - Pamphlets, 1946; 2 Items (Box 111, Folder 1370)
    - University of Illinois - Neurology, 1939-1948 (Box 111, Folder 1371)
    - University of Illinois - Neurology, 1939-1948 (Box 111, Folder 1372)
    - University of Illinois - Psychiatry, 1935-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1373)
    - University of Illinois - Psychiatry, 1935-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1374)
    - University of Illinois - Psychiatry, 1935-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1375)
    - University of Illinois - Psychiatry, 1935-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1376)
    - University of Michigan - Blumenthal, Franz - (Refugee Scholar, Dermatology), 1934-1941 (Box 112, Folder 1377)
    - University of Michigan - List, Carl F. - (Refugee Scholar, Neuro-Surgery), 1934-1939 (Box 112, Folder 1378)
    - University of Michigan - Medical Economics, 1935-1941 (Box 112, Folder 1379)
    - University of Michigan - Medical Economics, 1942-1954 (Box 113, Folder 1380)
    - University of Michigan - Medical Economics, 1942-1954 (Box 113, Folder 1381)
    - University of Michigan - Preventive Medicine, 1946-1947 (Box 113, Folder 1382)
    - University of Michigan - Psychiatry, 1933-1938 (Box 113, Folder 1383)
    - University of Michigan - Psychiatry, 1933-1938 (Box 113, Folder 1384)
    - University of Michigan - Psychiatry, 1933-1938 (Box 113, Folder 1385)
    - University of Oregon - Weinzirl, Adolph - Visit, Public Health, 1941-1942 (Box 113, Folder 1386)
    - University of Oregon - Weinzirl, Adolph - Visit, Public Health, 1941-1942 (Box 113, Folder 1387)
    - University of Oregon - Weinzirl, Adolph - Visit, Public Health - Report, 1941 (Box 113, Folder 1388)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Meyerhof, Otto - (Refugee Scholar, Physiology), January 1940-1951 (Box 113, Folder 1389)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Meyerhof, Otto - (Refugee Scholar, Physiology), January 1940-1951 (Box 113, Folder 1390)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Meyerhof, Otto - (Refugee Scholar, Physiology), January 1940-1951 (Box 113, Folder 1391)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Meyerhof, Otto - (Refugee Scholar, Physiology), January 1940-1951 (Box 113, Folder 1392)
    - University of Rochester - Dental Pathology, 1928-1933 (Box 113, Folder 1393)
    - University of Rochester - Dental Pathology, 1934-1942, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1394)
    - University of Rochester - Dental Pathology, 1934-1942, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 1395)
    - University of Rochester - Diathermy Studies, 1929-1939 (Box 114, Folder 1396)
    - University of Rochester - Diathermy Studies, 1929-1939 (Box 114, Folder 1397)
    - University of Rochester - Diathermy Studies, 1929-1939 (Box 114, Folder 1398)
    - University of Rochester - Diathermy Studies - Reports (Box 114, Folder 1399)
    - University of Rochester - Fischer, Ernst - (Refugee Scholar, Physiology), 1934-1936 (Box 114, Folder 1400)
    - University of Rochester - Fluid Research Fund, 1929-1935 (Box 114, Folder 1401)
    - University of Rochester - Fluid Research Fund, 1929-1935 (Box 114, Folder 1402)
    - University of Rochester - Fluid Research Fund - Reprints, 1931-1932; 9 Items (Box 114, Folder 1403)
    - University of Rochester - Fluid Research Fund, 1939-1945 (Box 114, Folder 1404)
    - University of Rochester - Fluid Research Fund, 1939-1945 (Box 114, Folder 1405)
    - University of Rochester - Psychiatry, 1928-1939 (Box 115, Folder 1406)
    - University of Rochester - Psychiatry, 1928-1939 (Box 115, Folder 1407)
    - University of Rochester - Psychiatry, 1928-1939 (Box 115, Folder 1408)
    - University of Rochester - Psychiatry, 1949-1950 (Box 115, Folder 1409)
    - University of Rochester - Respiration, 1934-1935 (Box 115, Folder 1410)
    - University of Rochester - Virus Research, 1935-1940 (Box 115, Folder 1411)
    - University of Tennessee - Psychiatry, 1937-1947 (Box 115, Folder 1412)
    - University of Tennessee - Psychiatry, 1937-1947 (Box 115, Folder 1413)
    - University of Tennessee - Psychiatry, 1937-1947 (Box 115, Folder 1414)
    - University of Utah - Child Psychiatry, 1943-1945 (Box 115, Folder 1415)
    - University of Utah - Fluid Research, 1943-1944 (Box 115, Folder 1416)
    - University of Utah - Fluid Research, 1943-1944 (Box 115, Folder 1417)
    - University of Utah - Fluid Research, 1945-1947 (Box 116, Folder 1418)
    - University of Utah - Young, Richard H. - (Visit, Medicine), 1947-1948 (Box 116, Folder 1419)
    - University of Vermont - Medical School, 1942-1943 (Box 116, Folder 1420)
    - University of Vermont - Raab, Wilhelm - (Refugee Scholar, Medicine), 1939-1942 (Box 116, Folder 1421)
    - University of Vermont - Raab, Wilhelm - (Refugee Scholar, Medicine), 1939-1942 (Box 116, Folder 1422)
    - University of Wisconsin - Zoology - (Visit, Collias, Nicholas E.), 1947-1949 (Box 116, Folder 1423)
    - Vanderbilt University - Fleming, Jane - (Visit, Hospital Records), 1943 (Box 116, Folder 1424)
    - Vanderbilt University - Leathers, W. S. - Visit, Public Health, 1935-1936 (Box 116, Folder 1425)
    - Vanderbilt University - Medical Care, 1943-1944 (Box 116, Folder 1426)
    - Vanderbilt University - Medical Sciences, 1929-1934 (Box 116, Folder 1427)
    - Vanderbilt University - Medical Sciences, 1929-1934 (Box 116, Folder 1428)
    - Vanderbilt University - Medical Sciences, 1938-1941, 1944 (Box 116, Folder 1429)
    - Vanderbilt University - Medical Sciences, 1938-1941, 1944 (Box 116, Folder 1430)
    - Vanderbilt University - Psychiatry, 1942-1948 (Box 116, Folder 1431)
    - Vanderbilt University - Psychiatry, 1942-1948 (Box 116, Folder 1432)
    - Vanderbilt University - Psychiatry, 1942-1948 (Box 116, Folder 1433)
    - Vanderbilt University - Wheeler, Ralph E. - (Visit, Epidemiology), 1942 (Box 116, Folder 1434)
    - Veterinary Medical Study, 1930-1939 (Box 117, Folder 1435)
    - Veterinary Medical Study, 1930-1939 (Box 117, Folder 1436)
    - Veterinary Medical Study - Reports, 1930; 2 Items (Box 117, Folder 1437)
    - Washington University - Dermatology, 1940-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1438)
    - Washington University - Dermatology, 1940-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1439)
    - Western Reserve University - Psychiatry, 1939-1940 (Box 117, Folder 1440)
    - Western Reserve University - Psychiatry, 1945-1954 (Box 117, Folder 1441)
    - Western Reserve University - Psychiatry, 1945-1954 (Box 117, Folder 1442)
    - William Alanson White Psychiatric Foundation - Sullivan, Harry S., 1941-1942 (Box 117, Folder 1443)
    - William Alanson White Psychiatric Foundation - Sullivan, Harry S., 1941-1942 (Box 117, Folder 1444)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1445)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1446)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1447)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1448)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1449)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1930-1941 (Box 117, Folder 1450)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox, 1942-1944 (Box 118, Folder 1451)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox - Reports, 1936-1942; 16 items contained in folders 1452-1455. (Box 118, Folder 1452)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox - Reports, 1936-1942; 16 items contained in folders 1452-1455. (Box 118, Folder 1453)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox - Reports, 1936-1942; 16 items contained in folders 1452-1455. (Box 118, Folder 1454)
    - Worcester State Hospital - Dementia Praecox - Reports, 1936-1942; 16 items contained in folders 1452-1455. (Box 118, Folder 1455)
    - Yale University - Alcohol Studies - Bioliography, 1947-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1456)
    - Yale University - Cahen, Raymond - (Refugee Scholar, Pharmacology), 1941-1944 (Box 118, Folder 1457)
    - Yale University - Cahen, Raymond - (Refugee Scholar, Pharmacology), 1941-1944 (Box 118, Folder 1458)
    - Yale University - Dental Pathology, 1928-1933 (Box 118, Folder 1459)
    - Yale University - Dental Pathology, 1928-1933 (Box 118, Folder 1460)
    - Yale University - Dental Pathology, 1934-1942 (Box 119, Folder 1461)
    - Yale University - Dental Pathology, 1934-1942 (Box 119, Folder 1462)
    - Yale University - Endocrinology, 1939-1943 (Box 119, Folder 1463)
    - Yale University - Endocrinology, 1939-1943 (Box 119, Folder 1464)
    - Yale University - Endocrinology - Reprints, 1931-1938; 9 Items (Box 119, Folder 1465)
    - Yale University - Fear and Courage Study, 1942-1944 (Box 119, Folder 1466)
    - Yale University - Fear and Courage Study, 1942-1944 (Box 119, Folder 1467)
    - Yale University - Fluid Research Fund, 1929-1939 (Box 119, Folder 1468)
    - Yale University - Fluid Research Fund, 1929-1939 (Box 119, Folder 1469)
    - Yale University - Fluid Research Fund - Reports, 1937-1938; 2 Items (Box 119, Folder 1470)
    - Yale University - Goldmann, Franz - Refugee Scholar, Public Health, 1937-1944 (Box 119, Folder 1471)
    - Yale University - Goldmann, Franz - Refugee Scholar, Public Health, 1937-1944 (Box 119, Folder 1472)
    - Yale University - Hiscock, Ira V. - (Visit, Medicine), 1934-1936 (Box 119, Folder 1473)
    - Yale University - Hiscock, Ira V. - (Visit, Medicine), 1954-1955 (Box 119, Folder 1474)
    - Yale University - Hiscock, Ira V. - (Visit, Medicine) - Report, 1935 (Box 119, Folder 1475)
    - Yale University - Neuroanatomy, 1934-1938 (Box 119, Folder 1476)
    - Yale University - Neuroanatomy - Reports, 1933-1936; 7 Items (Box 119, Folder 1477)
    - Yale University - Neuropathology, 1934-1939 (Box 120, Folder 1478)
    - Yale University - Neuropathology - Reports, 1933-1935; 2 Items (Box 120, Folder 1479)
    - Yale University - Neurophysiology, 1931-1941 (Box 120, Folder 1480)
    - Yale University - Neurophysiology, 1931-1941 (Box 120, Folder 1481)
    - Yale University - Neurophysiology - Reports and Reprints, 1932-1938; 7 Items (Box 120, Folder 1482)
    - Yale University - Pharmacology Conference, 1946-1947 (Box 120, Folder 1483)
    - Yale University - Psychiatry, 1937-1949 (Box 120, Folder 1484)
    - Yale University - Psychiatry, 1937-1949 (Box 120, Folder 1485)
    - Yale University - Psychiatry, 1937-1949 (Box 120, Folder 1486)
    - Yale University - Psychiatry - Redlich, Frederick, 1946-1955 (Box 120, Folder 1487)
    - Yale University - Public Health Teaching, 1940-1954 (Box 120, Folder 1488)
    - Yale University - Public Health Teaching, 1940-1954 (Box 120, Folder 1489)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing - Hulbert, Margaret, 1936, 1946-1949 (Box 120, Folder 1490)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing - Hulbert, Margaret, 1936, 1946-1949 (Box 120, Folder 1491)
  - United States - Nursing, 1914-1955; 200.C; 1 Cubic Feet; 3 __Boxes __1 cubic foot
    In this small subseries most of the material originated between the years 1918 and 1935. The files contain information relating to the development of public health nursing and to education for nurses in the eastern United States. Uniformity of standards in nurses training was the Foundation's main concern. At first the Foundation's program in nursing was administered by Edwin Embree as part of the program of the Division of Studies. After the reorganization of 1927-1938, nursing was transferred, first to the province of Richard M. Pearce and the Division of Medical Education, later to the International Health Division.
    Personnel in nursing in the Rockefeller Foundation included F. Elizabeth Crowell, who worked mostly in the field, and Mary Beard, former president of the National Organization for Public Health Nursing, who worked in the United States from 1925 to 1938. There is much of her correspondence in these files.
    For information about projects in nursing in other countries see the appropriate country number. Nursing Fellowship files are in Record Group 10, Fellowships. In the files of the Paris Office, Record Group 6 Field Offices, Subgroup 1, there are fellowship and general correspondence files pertaining to nursing.
    - Committee on Grading of Nursing Schools, 1926-1934 (Box 121, Folder 1492)
    - Committee on Grading of Nursing Schools, 1926-1934 (Box 121, Folder 1493)
    - Committee for the Study of Nursing Education, 1918-1924 (Box 121, Folder 1494)
    - Committee for the Study of Nursing Education, 1918-1924 (Box 121, Folder 1495)
    - Goodrich, Annie W. - (Travel Grant, PUMC), 1929-1930 (Box 121, Folder 1496)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Nursing School, 1917-1940 (Box 121, Folder 1497)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1914-1922 (Box 121, Folder 1498)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1914-1922 (Box 121, Folder 1499)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing - Report, 1920 (Box 121, Folder 1500)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1926 (Box 121, Folder 1501)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1931-1933 (Box 121, Folder 1502)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1931-1933 (Box 121, Folder 1503)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey, 1924-1927 (Box 121, Folder 1504)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey - Report: "Colored Nurses in Public Health Work" - NEN-1, 1924-1925 (Box 122, Folder 1505)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey - Report: "Colored Nurses in Public Health Work" - NEN-1, 1925 (Box 122, Folder 1506)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey - Johns, Ethel, "A Study of Present Status of the Negro Woman in Nursing" - NEN-2, 1925 (Box 122, Folder 1507)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey - "A Study of the Present Status of the Negro Woman in Nursing" - (and Supplementary Material 1920-1924) - NEN-2, 1920-1925 (Box 122, Folder 1508)
    - Nursing Education, Negro - Survey - "A Study of the Present Status of the Negro Woman in Nursing" - (and Supplementary Material 1920-1925) - NEN-2 (Box 122, Folder 1509)
    - Trudeau Foundation - School of Nursing, 1925-1930 (Box 122, Folder 1510)
    - Trudeau Foundation - School of Nursing, 1955 (Box 122, Folder 1511)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 122, Folder 1512)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 122, Folder 1513)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 122, Folder 1514)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 122, Folder 1515)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1924-1931 (Box 122, Folder 1516)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1932-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1517)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1932-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1518)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1932-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1519)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1932-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1520)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing, 1932-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1521)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing - Reports, 1930-1934; 11 items contained in folders 1522-1523. (Box 123, Folder 1522)
    - Vanderbilt University - School of Nursing - Reports, 1930-1934; 11 items contained in folders 1522-1523. (Box 123, Folder 1523)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1920-1927 (Box 123, Folder 1524)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1920-1927 (Box 123, Folder 1525)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1920-1927 (Box 123, Folder 1526)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1920-1927 (Box 123, Folder 1527)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 124, Folder 1528)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing, 1928-1941 (Box 124, Folder 1529)
    - Yale University - School of Nursing - Reports, 1924-1930; 3 Items (Box 124, Folder 1530)
  - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1921-1972; 200.D; 19 Cubic Feet; 45 __Boxes __19 cubic feet
    The Foundation's program in natural sciences developed from the old programs of the IEB and GEB. Under the direction of Wickliffe Rose, those organizations emphasized mathematics, physics, and chemistry. After a trial period, 1929-1932, during which the natural sciences division had five directors or acting directors, Warren Weaver was appointed director, remaining until 1951. A new program was developed, at first called "vital processes," later "modern experimental biology," to meet the desire of the Trustees for a people-oriented program based on the idea that the natural sciences were essential to medicine. The programs in medical science and natural science were intended to be complementary.
    This group of files contains material mostly from the 1930's and 40' relating to research projects in subjects such as biophysics, biochemistry, genetics and physiology. A number of European refugee scholars were aided under this program. The application of physical and chemical techniques to biology, genetics and nutrition was of special interest. There are no files relating to agriculture in this subseries.
    - American Documentation Institute - Bibliofilm Service, 1936-1940 (Box 124, Folder 1531)
    - American Geophysical Union, 1943-1947 (Box 124, Folder 1532)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1930-1942 (Box 124, Folder 1533)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1930-1942 (Box 124, Folder 1534)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1930-1942 (Box 124, Folder 1535)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1930-1942 (Box 124, Folder 1536)
    - American Institute of Physics - Report, 1942 (Box 124, Folder 1537)
    - American Institute of Physics - Reports - Financial, 1940-1941 (Box 124, Folder 1538)
    - American Institute of Physics - War Policy Committee, 1942-1944 (Box 124, Folder 1539)
    - American Institute of Physics - War Policy Committee, 1945-1949 (Box 125, Folder 1540)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1929-1940 (Box 125, Folder 1541)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1929-1940 (Box 125, Folder 1542)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1929-1940 (Box 125, Folder 1543)
    - American Mathematical Society, 1929-1940 (Box 125, Folder 1544)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Congress of Mathematicians, 1937-1941 (Box 125, Folder 1545)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Congress of Mathematicians, 1946-1952 (Box 125, Folder 1546)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Congress of Mathematicians - Reports, 1936-1937; 4 Items (Box 125, Folder 1547)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Congress of Mathematicians - Reports (Published), 1950 (Box 125, Folder 1548)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, 1937-February 1939 (Box 125, Folder 1549)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, 1937-February 1939 (Box 125, Folder 1550)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1551)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1552)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1553)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1554)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1555)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1556)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1557)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal, March 1939-1950 (Box 126, Folder 1558)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal - Reports, 1934-1940; 6 Items (Box 126, Folder 1559)
    - American Mathematical Society - International Review Journal - Reports and Reprints, 1921-1928; 18 Items (Box 126, Folder 1560)
    - American Mathematical Society - War Policy Commission, 1943-1947 (Box 127, Folder 1561)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers - Earthquake Investigations - Historical Record, 1930-1932 (Box 127, Folder 1562)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1563)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1564)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1565)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1566)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1567)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1934-1951 (Box 127, Folder 1568)
    - Amherst College - Biology, 1952-1964 (Box 128, Folder 1569)
    - Amherst College - Biology - Reports - Financial, 1941-1944 (Box 128, Folder 1570)
    - Amherst College - Drosophila Genetics, 1940-1945 (Box 128, Folder 1571)
    - Amherst College - Drosophila Genetics, 1940-1945 (Box 128, Folder 1572)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Cellulose Research, 1940 (Box 128, Folder 1573)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Cellulose Research - Report, 1940 (Box 128, Folder 1574)
    - Brush Foundation - Rubenstein, Boris B. - (Sex Research), 1936-1941, 1943 (Box 128, Folder 1575)
    - Brush Foundation - Rubenstein, Boris B. - (Sex Research), 1936-1941, 1943 (Box 128, Folder 1576)
    - Brush Foundation - Rubenstein, Boris B. - (Sex Research), 1936-1941, 1943 (Box 128, Folder 1577)
    - Brush Foundation - Rubenstein, Boris B. - (Sex Research) - Reports - Financial, 1936-1939; 4 Items (Box 128, Folder 1578)
    - Brush Foundation - Rubenstein, Boris B. - (Sex Research) - Reprints and Photographs, 1937-1939; 3 Items (Box 128, Folder 1579)
    - Bryn Mawr College - Noether, Emmy - (Refugee Scholar, Mathematics), 1933-1936 (Box 128, Folder 1580)
    - Carnegie Institute of Washington - Embryology, 1935-1939 (Box 128, Folder 1581)
    - Carnegie Institute of Washington - Endocrinology, 1936-1937 (Box 128, Folder 1582)
    - Carnegie Institute of Washington - Endocrinology, 1938-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1583)
    - Carnegie Institute of Washington - Endocrinology, 1938-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1584)
    - Carnegie Institute of Washington - Endocrinology - Report, 1938 (Box 129, Folder 1585)
    - Catholic University - Organic Chemistry, 1939-1941 (Box 129, Folder 1586)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1930 (Box 129, Folder 1587)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1588)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1589)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1590)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1591)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station, 1929-1942 (Box 129, Folder 1592)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station - Reports, 1931-1934 (Box 129, Folder 1593)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station - Reports (Published), 1932-1941; 6 Items (Box 129, Folder 1594)
    - Central Atlantic Oceanographic Station - Reports - Financial, 1931-1936; 7 Items (Box 129, Folder 1595)